[{"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115573", "answer": "\ufeffarbeiten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: arbeitete", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: gearbeitet", "question": "\uc77c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115611", "answer": "begr\u00fc\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: begr\u00fc\u00dfte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: begr\u00fc\u00dft", "question": "\uc778\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115624", "answer": "hei\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hie\u00df", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: gehei\u00dfen", "question": "\ubd88\ub9ac\uc6b0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115635", "answer": "kommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kam", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: gekommen", "question": "\uc624\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115644", "answer": "korrigieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: korrigierte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: korrigiert", "question": "\ucca8\uc0ad\ud558\ub2e4, \uace0\uce58\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115655", "answer": "malen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: malte", "chunk": 0, "info2": "Partizip II: gemalt", "question": "\uadf8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115664", "answer": "passen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: gepasst", "question": "\uc54c\ub9de\ub2e4, \uc5b4\uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115674", "answer": "sammeln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sammelte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: gesammelt", "question": "\ubaa8\uc73c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115683", "answer": "sein", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: war", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: gewesen", "question": "~\uc774\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115692", "answer": "tauschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tauschte", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: getauscht", "question": "\uad50\ud658\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115702", "answer": "vorstellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stellte...vor", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: vorgestellt", "question": "\uc18c\uac1c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115711", "answer": "beginnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: begann", "chunk": 1, "info2": "Partizip II: begonnen", "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115720", "answer": "besuchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: besuchte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: besucht", "question": "\ubc29\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115729", "answer": "brauchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brauchte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: gebraucht", "question": "\ud544\uc694\ub85c \ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115738", "answer": "finden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fand", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: gefunden", "question": "\ucc3e\ub2e4, \uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115749", "answer": "funktionieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: funktionierte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: funktioniert", "question": "\uc791\ub3d9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115759", "answer": "geben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gab", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: gegeben", "question": "\uc8fc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115768", "answer": "erg\u00e4nzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erg\u00e4nzte", "chunk": 2, "info2": "Partizip II: erg\u00e4nzt", "question": "\ucc44\uc6cc \ub123\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115778", "answer": "gefallen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gefiel", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gefallen", "question": "~\uc758 \ub9c8\uc74c\uc5d0 \ub4e4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115788", "answer": "gehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ging", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gegangen", "question": "\uac00\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115797", "answer": "gr\u00fcnden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gr\u00fcndete", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gegr\u00fcndet", "question": "\uae30\ucd08\ub85c \ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115809", "answer": "gr\u00fc\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gr\u00fc\u00dfte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gegr\u00fc\u00dft", "question": "\uc548\ubd80\ub97c \uc804\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115819", "answer": "haben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hatte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gehabt", "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115828", "answer": "kennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kannte", "chunk": 3, "info2": "Partizip II: gekannt", "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115837", "answer": "lernen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lernte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: gelernt", "question": "\ubc30\uc6b0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115847", "answer": "machen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: machte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: gemacht", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4, \ub9cc\ub4e4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115856", "answer": "planen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: plante", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: geplant", "question": "\uacc4\ud68d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115865", "answer": "tanzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tanzte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: getanzt", "question": "\ucda4\ucd94\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115874", "answer": "lesen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: las", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: gelesen", "question": "\uc77d\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115883", "answer": "telefonieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: telefonierte", "chunk": 4, "info2": "Partizip II: telefoniert", "question": "\uc804\ud654\ub97c \uac78\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115893", "answer": "zeigen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: zeigte", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: gezeigt", "question": "\ubcf4\uc5ec\uc8fc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115904", "answer": "essen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: a\u00df", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: gegessen", "question": "\uba39\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115913", "answer": "trinken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trank", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: getrunken", "question": "\ub9c8\uc2dc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115922", "answer": "besprechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: besprach", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: besprochen", "question": "\ud611\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115931", "answer": "erz\u00e4hlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erz\u00e4hlte", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: erz\u00e4hlt", "question": "\uc774\uc57c\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115941", "answer": "kosten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kostete", "chunk": 5, "info2": "Partizip II: gekostet", "question": "\ube44\uc6a9\uc774 \ub4e4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115950", "answer": "tun", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: tat", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: getan", "question": "\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115959", "answer": "vergleichen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verglich", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: verglichen", "question": "\ube44\uad50\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115968", "answer": "bekommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bekam", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: bekommen", "question": "\ubc1b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115977", "answer": "bezahlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bezahlte", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: bezahlt", "question": "\uc9c0\ubd88\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115986", "answer": "erlauben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erlaubte", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: erlaubt", "question": "\ud5c8\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.115995", "answer": "fahren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fuhr", "chunk": 6, "info2": "Partizip II: gefahren", "question": "\ud0c0\uace0 \uac00\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116006", "answer": "feiern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: feierte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: gefeiert", "question": "\uae30\ub150\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116016", "answer": "tragen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trug", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: getragen", "question": "\uc6b4\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116025", "answer": "klingeln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: klingelte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: geklingelt", "question": "\ubca8\uc774 \uc6b8\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116034", "answer": "ankommen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kam\u2026an", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: angekommen", "question": "\ub3c4\ucc29\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116043", "answer": "bewundern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bewunderte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: bewundert", "question": "\uacbd\ud0c4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116053", "answer": "organisieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: organisierte", "chunk": 7, "info2": "Partizip II: organisiert", "question": "\uc870\uc9c1\ud558\ub2e4, \ud615\uc131\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116062", "answer": "passieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passierte", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: passiert", "question": "\ubc1c\uc0dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116071", "answer": "putzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: putzte", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: geputzt", "question": "\uccad\uc18c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116080", "answer": "schaffen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schuf", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: geschaffen", "question": "\ucc3d\uc870\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116091", "answer": "schlafen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schlief", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: geschlafen", "question": "\uc790\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116100", "answer": "schauen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schaute", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: geschaut", "question": "\ubc14\ub77c\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116109", "answer": "sehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah", "chunk": 8, "info2": "Partizip II: gesehen", "question": "\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116118", "answer": "st\u00fcrzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: st\u00fcrzte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: gest\u00fcrzt", "question": "\ucd94\ub77d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116127", "answer": "suchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: suchte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: gesucht", "question": "\ucc3e\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116136", "answer": "treffen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: traf", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: getroffen", "question": "\ub9cc\ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116145", "answer": "wissen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wusste", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: gewusst", "question": "\uc54c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116154", "answer": "w\u00fcnschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: w\u00fcnschte", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: gew\u00fcnscht", "question": "\uc6d0\ud558\ub2e4, \ubc14\ub77c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116163", "answer": "abholen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: holte...ab", "chunk": 9, "info2": "Partizip II: abgeholt", "question": "\ub370\ub9ac\ub7ec \uac00\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116175", "answer": "aufmachen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: machte...auf", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: aufgemacht", "question": "\uc5f4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116184", "answer": "ausgehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ging...aus", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgegangen", "question": "\uc548\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116193", "answer": "schneiden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schnitt", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: geschnitten", "question": "\uc790\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116202", "answer": "anrufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rief...an", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: angerufen", "question": "\ud1b5\ud654\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116211", "answer": "antworten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: antwortete", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: geantwortet", "question": "\ub300\ub2f5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116220", "answer": "anschauen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schaute...an", "chunk": 10, "info2": "Partizip II: angeschaut", "question": "\uc751\uc2dc\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116229", "answer": "singen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sang", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: gesungen", "question": "\ub178\ub798\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116238", "answer": "aussehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah...aus", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgesehen", "question": "~\ub85c \ubcf4\uc774\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116247", "answer": "benutzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: benutzte", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: benutzt", "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116256", "answer": "beschreiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: beschrieb", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: beschrieben", "question": "\ubb18\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116269", "answer": "bleiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: blieb", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: geblieben", "question": "\uba38\ubb34\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116281", "answer": "dauern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dauerte", "chunk": 11, "info2": "Partizip II: gedauert", "question": "\uc2dc\uac04\uc774 \uac78\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116291", "answer": "denken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dachte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: gedacht", "question": "\uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116300", "answer": "duschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: duschte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: geduscht", "question": "\uc0e4\uc6cc\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116309", "answer": "erreichen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erreichte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: erreicht", "question": "\ub3c4\ub2ec\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116318", "answer": "glauben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: glaubte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: geglaubt", "question": "\ubbff\ub2e4, \uc0dd\uac01\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116327", "answer": "informieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: informierte", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: informiert", "question": "\uc815\ubcf4\ub97c \uc8fc\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116336", "answer": "mitbringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brachte\u2026mit", "chunk": 12, "info2": "Partizip II: mitgebracht", "question": "\ub370\ub9ac\uace0 \uc624\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116345", "answer": "abfahren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fuhr\u2026ab", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: abgefahren", "question": "\ucd9c\ubc1c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116358", "answer": "bestellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bestellte", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: bestellt", "question": "\uc8fc\ubb38\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116369", "answer": "reden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: redete", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: geredet", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116378", "answer": "regnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: regnete", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: geregnet", "question": "\ube44\uac00 \uc624\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116387", "answer": "reparieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: reparierte", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: repariert", "question": "\uc218\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116396", "answer": "sitzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sa\u00df", "chunk": 13, "info2": "Partizip II: gesessen", "question": "\uc549\uc544 \uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116405", "answer": "stehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stand", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: gestanden", "question": "\uc11c \uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116415", "answer": "messen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: ma\u00df", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: gemessen", "question": "\uce21\uc815\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116424", "answer": "verbringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verbrachte", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: verbracht", "question": "\uc2dc\uac04\uc744 \ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116435", "answer": "vergessen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verga\u00df", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: vergessen", "question": "\uc78a\uc5b4\ubc84\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116447", "answer": "verwenden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verwendete", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: verwendet", "question": "\uc0ac\uc6a9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116456", "answer": "wechseln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wechselte", "chunk": 14, "info2": "Partizip II: gewechselt", "question": "\uad50\uccb4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116465", "answer": "fehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fehlte", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: gefehlt", "question": "\ubd80\uc871\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116474", "answer": "anfangen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fing...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: angefangen", "question": "\uc2dc\uc791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116483", "answer": "anprobieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: probierte...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: anprobiert", "question": "\uc785\uc5b4\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116495", "answer": "ansto\u00dfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sto\u00dfte...an", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: angesto\u00dft", "question": "\ubc00\uce58\ub2e4, \uac74\ubc30\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116506", "answer": "aufpassen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: passte\u2026auf", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: aufgepasst", "question": "\uc8fc\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116515", "answer": "ausf\u00fchren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: f\u00fchrte...aus", "chunk": 15, "info2": "Partizip II: ausgef\u00fchrt", "question": "\uc218\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116526", "answer": "bedeuten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bedeutete", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: bedeutet", "question": "\uc758\ubbf8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116538", "answer": "bringen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brachte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: gebracht", "question": "\uac00\uc9c0\uace0 \uc624\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116547", "answer": "kaufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kaufte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: gekauft", "question": "\uad6c\ub9e4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116556", "answer": "eingeben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gab...ein", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: eingegeben", "question": "\ubcf5\uc6a9\uc2dc\ud0a4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116565", "answer": "einladen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lud...ein", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: eingeladen", "question": "\ucd08\ub300\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116573", "answer": "entschuldigen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: entschuldigte", "chunk": 16, "info2": "Partizip II: entschuldigt", "question": "\uc6a9\uc11c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116582", "answer": "erkl\u00e4ren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: erkl\u00e4rte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: erkl\u00e4rt", "question": "\uc124\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116591", "answer": "fernsehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sah...fern", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: ferngesehen", "question": "TV\ub97c \ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116600", "answer": "festhalten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hielt\u2026fest", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: festgehalten", "question": "\ubd99\uc7a1\ub2e4, \uace0\uc9d1\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116610", "answer": "helfen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: half", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: geholfen", "question": "\ub3d5\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116621", "answer": "holen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: holte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: geholt", "question": "\uac00\uc838\uc624\ub2e4, \uaebc\ub0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116631", "answer": "kopieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kopierte", "chunk": 17, "info2": "Partizip II: kopiert", "question": "\ubcf5\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116643", "answer": "l\u00e4cheln", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: l\u00e4chelte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: gel\u00e4chelt", "question": "\ubbf8\uc18c\ub97c \uc9d3\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116652", "answer": "mailen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: mailte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: gemailt", "question": "\uba54\uc77c\uc744 \ubcf4\ub0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116662", "answer": "nachfragen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: fragte\u2026nach", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: nachgefragt", "question": "\ubb38\uc758\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116670", "answer": "nehmen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: nahm", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: genommen", "question": "\ucde8\ud558\ub2e4, \uac00\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116680", "answer": "nennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: nannte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: genannt", "question": "\uba85\uba85\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116689", "answer": "sagen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sagte", "chunk": 18, "info2": "Partizip II: gesagt", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116697", "answer": "empfehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: empfahl", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: empfohlen", "question": "\ucd94\ucc9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116706", "answer": "fliegen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: flog", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: geflogen", "question": "\ub0a0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116715", "answer": "tr\u00e4umen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: t\u00e4umte", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: getr\u00e4umt", "question": "\uafc8\uafb8\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116728", "answer": "vermuten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: vermutete", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: vermutet", "question": "\ucd94\uce21\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116737", "answer": "versuchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: versuchte", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: versucht", "question": "\uc2dc\ub3c4\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116746", "answer": "warten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wartete", "chunk": 19, "info2": "Partizip II: gewartet", "question": "\uae30\ub2e4\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116755", "answer": "beenden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: beendete", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: beendet", "question": "\ub05d\ub0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116764", "answer": "laufen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lief", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: gelaufen", "question": "\ub2ec\ub9ac\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116776", "answer": "danken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dankte", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: gedankt", "question": "\uac10\uc0ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116788", "answer": "lassen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lie\u00df", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: gelassen", "question": "\ud558\uac8c \ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116797", "answer": "aufr\u00e4umen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: r\u00e4umte...auf", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: aufger\u00e4umt", "question": "\uc815\ub9ac\uc815\ub3c8\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116806", "answer": "h\u00f6ren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: h\u00f6rte", "chunk": 20, "info2": "Partizip II: geh\u00f6rt", "question": "\ub4e3\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116818", "answer": "treiben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: trieb", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: getrieben", "question": "\ubab0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116827", "answer": "heiraten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: heiratete", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: geheiratet", "question": "\uacb0\ud63c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116836", "answer": "lachen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lachte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: gelacht", "question": "\uc6c3\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116845", "answer": "leben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lebte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: gelebt", "question": "\uc0b4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116856", "answer": "reisen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: reiste", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: gereist", "question": "\uc5ec\ud589\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116865", "answer": "schmecken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schmeckte", "chunk": 21, "info2": "Partizip II: geschmeckt", "question": "\ub9db\uc774 \ub098\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116875", "answer": "sterben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: starb", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: gestorben", "question": "\uc8fd\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116883", "answer": "studieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: studierte", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: studiert", "question": "\uc804\uacf5\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116892", "answer": "verstehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verstand", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: verstanden", "question": "\uc774\ud574\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116903", "answer": "schwimmen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schwamm", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: geschwommen", "question": "\uc218\uc601\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116915", "answer": "unterrichten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: unterrichtete", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: unterrichtet", "question": "\uc218\uc5c5\uc744 \ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116924", "answer": "werden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wurde", "chunk": 22, "info2": "Partizip II: geworden", "question": "\ub418\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116933", "answer": "gewinnen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: gewann", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: gewonnen", "question": "\uc774\uae30\ub2e4, \uc5bb\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116942", "answer": "lieben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: liebte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: geliebt", "question": "\uc0ac\ub791\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116951", "answer": "stehlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stahl", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: gestohlen", "question": "\ud6d4\uce58\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116962", "answer": "probieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: probierte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: probiert", "question": "\ud574\ubcf4\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116971", "answer": "zahlen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: zahlte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: gezahlt", "question": "\uac12\uc744 \uce58\ub974\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116980", "answer": "dekorieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: dekorierte", "chunk": 23, "info2": "Partizip II: dekoriert", "question": "\uc7a5\uc2dd\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.116990", "answer": "schenken", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: schenkte", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: geschenkt", "question": "\uc120\ubb3c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117001", "answer": "brechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brach", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: gebrochen", "question": "\uae68\ub2e4, \ubd80\ub7ec\uc9c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117010", "answer": "buchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: buchte", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: gebucht", "question": "\uc608\uc57d\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117019", "answer": "l\u00fcgen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: log", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: gelogen", "question": "\uac70\uc9d3\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117028", "answer": "sprechen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: sprach", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: gesprochen", "question": "\ub9d0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117038", "answer": "h\u00e4ngen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: hing", "chunk": 24, "info2": "Partizip II: gehangen", "question": "\uac78\ub2e4, \uac78\ub824\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117049", "answer": "liegen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: lag", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: gelegen", "question": "\ub215\ud788\ub2e4, \ub193\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117058", "answer": "legen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: legte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: gelegt", "question": "\ub193\uc5ec\uc788\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117068", "answer": "spielen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: spielte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: gespielt", "question": "\ub180\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117076", "answer": "stellen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: stellte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: gestellt", "question": "\uc138\uc6cc\ub450\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117085", "answer": "bestehen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: bestand", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: bestanden", "question": "\ud569\uaca9\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117096", "answer": "kochen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: kochte", "chunk": 25, "info2": "Partizip II: gekocht", "question": "\uc694\ub9ac\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117105", "answer": "teilen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: teilte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: geteilt", "question": "\ub098\ub204\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117114", "answer": "waschen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wusch", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: gewaschen", "question": "\uc53b\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117123", "answer": "brennen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: brannte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: gebrannt", "question": "\ubd88\uc5d0 \ud0c0\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117134", "answer": "wandern", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: wanderte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: gewandert", "question": "\ub4f1\ubc18\ud558\ub2e4, \uac77\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117144", "answer": "\u00fcbersetzen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: \u00fcbersetzte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: \u00fcbersetzt", "question": "\ubc88\uc5ed\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117153", "answer": "rauchen", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rauchte", "chunk": 26, "info2": "Partizip II: geraucht", "question": "\ub2f4\ubc30\ub97c \ud53c\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117162", "answer": "verschieben", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verschob", "chunk": 27, "info2": "Partizip II: verschoben", "question": "\uc5f0\uae30\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117171", "answer": "verbinden", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: verband", "chunk": 27, "info2": "Partizip II: verbunden", "question": "\uc5f0\uacb0\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117182", "answer": "retten", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: rettete", "chunk": 27, "info2": "Partizip II: gerettet", "question": "\uad6c\ucd9c\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}, {"date": "2018-12-24 00:17:26.117200", "answer": "spazieren", "difficulty": 2, "info1": "Pr\u00e4sens: spazierte", "chunk": 27, "info2": "Partizip II: spaziert", "question": "\uc0b0\ucc45\ud558\ub2e4", "learned": false}]